0
['US territory of Guam in the Pacific smashed by Typhoon Mawar (2023-05-25)'
 'Guam braces for  category 5  Typhoon Mawar as pray for Guam trends on Twitter (2023-05-23)'
 'Guam braces itself for  direct hit  from Typhoon Mawar (2023-05-23)'
 'Typhoon Mawar Passes Over Pacific Island of Guam (2023-05-24)'
 'Guam  Weathers Storm  As Typhoon Mawar Moves West (2023-05-25)']
["{'entity_type': {'US': 'GPE', 'Guam': 'GPE', 'Pacific': 'LOC', 'Typhoon Mawar': 'FAC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Territory of Guam': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16635', 'Guam': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16635', 'Pacific': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q98', 'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Guam': 'GPE', '5': 'CARDINAL', 'Typhoon Mawar': 'FAC', 'Twitter': 'PRODUCT'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Guam': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16635', 'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384', 'category': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q719395', 'Pray': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q42234419', 'Twitter': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q918'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Guam': 'GPE', 'Typhoon Mawar': 'FAC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Guam': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16635', 'Direct Hit': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q18719089', 'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Typhoon Mawar Passes Over Pacific Island of': 'EVENT', 'Guam': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384', 'Island': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q189', 'Over': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q20020605', 'Guam': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16635'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Guam  Weathers Storm': 'ORG', 'Typhoon Mawar Moves West': 'EVENT'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Guam': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16635', 'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
1
['India Mumbai hit by Cyclone Biparjoy , flight operations affected (2023-06-12)'
 'Cyclone Biparjoy to cross near Jakhau Port in Gujarat on June 15 : IMD (2023-06-12)'
 'Pakistan : Tropical Cyclone Biparjoy - Flash Update No . 2 ( As of 13 June 2023 PM ) - Pakistan (2023-06-14)'
 'Tropical Cyclone Biparjoy - Jun 2023 (2023-06-13)'
 'Pakistan : Tropical Cyclone Biparjoy - Flash Update No . 1 ( As of 12 June 2023 PM ) - Pakistan (2023-06-13)']
["{'entity_type': {'India': 'GPE', 'Mumbai': 'GPE', 'Cyclone Biparjoy': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'flight': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q13583449'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Cyclone Biparjoy': 'PERSON', 'Jakhau Port': 'FAC', 'Gujarat': 'GPE', 'June 15': 'DATE', 'IMD': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Port': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q191034', 'Gujarat': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1061', 'June': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q120', 'IMD': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q328692'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Pakistan': 'GPE', '2': 'CARDINAL', '13 June 2023 PM': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Pakistan': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q843', 'Flash': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15711398', '.': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q172008', 'PM': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q180686', 'June': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q120'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Jun': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q120'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Pakistan': 'GPE', '1': 'CARDINAL', '12 June 2023 PM': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Pakistan': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q843', 'Flash': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15711398', '.': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q172008', 'PM': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q180686', 'June': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q120'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
2
['India - Tropical cyclone Tauktae ( DG ECHO partners , government , IMD , local media ) ( ECHO Daily Flash of 15 May 2021 ) - India (2021-05-15)'
 'Cyclone Tauktae expected to become very severe : IMD (2021-05-15)'
 'Cyclone Tauktae likely to intensify into a cyclonic storm (2021-05-14)'
 'Subject : Cyclonic Storm  Tauktae  ( pronounced as TauTe ) over Gujarat region , TIME OF ISSUE : 1950 HOURS IST DATED : 18 . 05 . 2021 - India (2021-05-18)'
 'India , Pakistan - Tropical Cyclone TAUKTAE ( DG ECHO , GDACS , JTWC , IMD , NDM India ) ( ECHO Daily Flash of 18 May 2021 ) - India (2021-05-18)']
["{'entity_type': {'India': 'GPE', 'IMD': 'ORG', 'ECHO Daily Flash': 'ORG', '15 May 2021': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'partner': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q728646', 'tropical cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8092', 'government': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7188', 'IMD': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q328692', 'media': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1740954', 'Flash': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15711398', 'May': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q119', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Cyclone Tauktae': 'ORG', 'IMD': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'IMD': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q328692'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Cyclone Tauktae': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Gujarat': 'GPE', 'TIME OF ISSUE': 'ORG', '1950 HOURS': 'DATE', '18': 'CARDINAL', '2021': 'DATE', 'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Subject': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7631370', 'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Gujarat': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1061', 'TIME': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7670399', 'Issue': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q6088376', 'Hours': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q157044', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'India': 'GPE', 'Pakistan': 'GPE', 'DG ECHO': 'ORG', 'GDACS': 'ORG', 'JTWC': 'ORG', 'IMD': 'ORG', 'NDM India': 'ORG', '18 May 2021': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Flash': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15711398', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668', 'tropical cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8092', 'ECHO': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q709571', 'IMD': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q328692', 'May': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q119'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
3
['Salvation army undertakes emergency food distributions as cyclone Eloise hits Mozambique - Mozambique (2021-01-28)'
 'Communities in Mozambique devastated by Cyclone Eloise (2021-01-28)'
 'CARE Responds to Cyclone Eloise in Mozambique , Early Assessments Show Disaster Preparedness Paid Off (2021-01-28)'
 'Frightened Residents Brace as Tropical Storm Eloise Approaches Mozambique - Mozambique (2021-01-22)'
 'CARE offices in Mozambique and Zimbabwe prepare to respond as Storm Eloise looks set to worsen into a Cyclone over the weekend - Mozambique (2021-01-22)']
["{'entity_type': {'Eloise': 'PERSON', 'Mozambique - Mozambique': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Salvation Army': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q188307', 'food distribution': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5465458', 'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Mozambique': 'GPE', 'Cyclone Eloise': 'PRODUCT'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Communities': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5154560', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Mozambique': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'CARE': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q699385', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029', 'disaster preparedness': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1460420', 'Off': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7078915'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Frightened Residents Brace as Tropical Storm Eloise Approaches Mozambique - Mozambique': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Residents': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q947955', 'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232', 'Eloise': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3051638', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Mozambique': 'GPE', 'Zimbabwe': 'GPE', 'Storm Eloise': 'ORG', 'Cyclone': 'LOC', 'the weekend - Mozambique': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'office': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q12823105', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029', 'Zimbabwe': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q954', 'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Weekend': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2628694'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
4
['Cyclone Sitrang : 24 dead as Bangladesh seeks to restore power to millions (2022-10-26)'
 '12 People Killed , 10 , 000 Houses Damaged by Cyclone Sitrang in Bangladesh , October 25 , 2022 (2022-10-27)'
 '16 dead as cyclone pounds Bangladesh coast (2022-10-25)'
 '28 Dead In Bangladesh Cyclone , Millions Without Power (2022-10-26)'
 'Deadly cyclone leaves millions of Bangladeshis without electricity (2022-10-25)']
["{'entity_type': {'24': 'CARDINAL', 'Bangladesh': 'GPE', 'millions': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Bangladesh': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q902', 'power': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q25342', 'million': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q38526'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'12': 'CARDINAL', '10': 'DATE', '000': 'CARDINAL', 'Cyclone Sitrang': 'ORG', 'Bangladesh': 'GPE', 'October 25 , 2022': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'People': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q33659', 'House': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q23558', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Bangladesh': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q902', 'October': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q124'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'16': 'CARDINAL', 'Bangladesh': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'28': 'CARDINAL', 'Millions': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Dead': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q504434', 'Bangladesh': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q902', 'Millions': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1854561', 'Power': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15072855'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'millions': 'CARDINAL', 'Bangladeshis': 'NORP'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602', 'million': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q38526', 'Bangladeshis': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4855428', 'electricity': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q12725'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
5
['New Zealand Auckland braces for ex - cyclone Gabrielle impact – The Times Of Earth (2023-02-12)'
 'Cyclone Gabrielle : New Zealand residents on alert for  severe weather  as Hipkins government says :  Time to plan and prepare   (2023-02-10)'
 'Cyclone Gabrielle is on the way (2023-02-10)'
 'Auckland braces for the impact of ex - cyclone Gabrielle (2023-02-12)'
 'Auckland braces for impact of ex - cyclone Gabrielle after Norfolk Island misses worst (2023-02-12)']
["{'entity_type': {'New Zealand Auckland': 'GPE', 'Gabrielle': 'PERSON', 'The Times Of Earth': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Auckland': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q37100', 'ex': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q9968', 'Times': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q50008', 'Earth': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'New Zealand': 'GPE', 'Hipkins': 'PERSON', 'Time': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'New': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q14754876', 'alert': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4716232', 'severe weather': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q741507', 'government': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7188', 'Time': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q43297'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Cyclone Gabrielle': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'way': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q17641254'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Auckland': 'PERSON', 'Gabrielle': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Auckland': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q37100', 'impact': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4115667', 'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Auckland': 'PERSON', 'Gabrielle': 'PERSON', 'Norfolk Island': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Auckland': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q37100', 'impact': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4115667', 'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602', 'Norfolk Island': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q31057'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
6
['Death toll climbs past 110 in European floods (2021-07-16)'
 'Death toll rises to 33 as severe floods hit China Henan (2021-07-22)'
 'Death toll from China floods climbs to 51 (2021-07-23)'
 'Europe Reels From Worst Floods In Years As Death Toll Passes 120 (2021-07-16)'
 'Nearly 130 people die : Europe shocked by floods (2021-07-17)']
["{'entity_type': {'110': 'CARDINAL', 'European': 'NORP'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'33': 'CARDINAL', 'China': 'GPE', 'Henan': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654', 'China': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q148'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'China': 'GPE', '51': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'China': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q148'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Europe Reels From Worst Floods': 'WORK_OF_ART', 'Years': 'DATE', '120': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Europe': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q458', 'Flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3363652', 'Years': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8050960', 'Death': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q161936'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Nearly 130': 'CARDINAL', 'Europe': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'people': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5', 'Europe': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q458', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
7
['Tropical Storm Elsa Situation Report No . 3 as of 4 : 00pm on July 6 , 2021 - Haiti (2021-07-07)'
 'Tropical storm Elsa batters Cuban and Florida coasts - Israel National News (2021-07-04)'
 'Live Report As Storm Elsa Batters The East Coast Of America (2021-07-09)'
 'Central Cuba bracing for tropical storm Elsa (2021-07-05)'
 'Tropical Storm Elsa had sustained winds of 62 mph (2021-07-04)']
["{'entity_type': {'3': 'CARDINAL', '4': 'CARDINAL', 'July 6 , 2021 -': 'DATE', 'Haiti': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Report': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3107469', '.': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q172008', 'Haiti': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q790', 'July': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q121'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Elsa': 'PERSON', 'Cuban': 'NORP', 'Florida': 'GPE', 'Israel National News': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232', 'Elsa': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15620419', 'coast': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q93352', 'Israel National News': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q716861'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'The East Coast Of America': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Live Report': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1333641', 'Elsa': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15620419', 'East Coast': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4268', 'America': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Central Cuba': 'LOC', 'Elsa': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cuba': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q241', 'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232', 'Elsa': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15620419'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Tropical Storm Elsa': 'ORG', '62 mph': 'QUANTITY'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Elsa': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15620419', 'wind': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8094', 'mph': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q211256'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
8
['Tropical storm Nalgae death toll in Philippines nearly 100 (2022-10-31)'
 'Death toll from floods , landslides in south Philippines rises to 31 (2022-10-28)'
 'Death toll from floods and landslides in southern Philippines climbs to 72 (2022-10-29)'
 'Floods , landslides in Philippine south kill at least 26 (2022-10-28)'
 'Death toll rises to 45 as tropical storm hits Philippines (2022-10-29)']
["{'entity_type': {'Nalgae': 'GPE', 'Philippines': 'GPE', 'nearly 100': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'Philippines': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q928'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Philippines': 'GPE', '31': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654', 'landslide': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q167903', 'Philippines': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q928'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Philippines': 'GPE', '72': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654', 'landslide': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q167903', 'Philippines': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q928'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Philippine': 'NORP', 'at least 26': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3363652', 'landslide': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q167903'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'45': 'CARDINAL', 'Philippines': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232', 'Philippines': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q928'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
9
['Humanitarian Crisis Feared as Cyclone Kills 20 in Madagascar (2022-02-07)'
 'Cyclone Batsirai pounds Madagascar (2022-02-06)'
 'Cyclone Batsirai : Madagascar braced for second cyclone in weeks (2022-02-04)'
 'BBC World Service - Newshour , Cyclone Batsirai : Madagascar hospitals and schools destroyed (2022-02-12)'
 'Intense Cyclone Batsirai hits Madagascar : meteorologist (2022-02-05)']
["{'entity_type': {'20': 'CARDINAL', 'Madagascar': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'humanitarian crisis': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q617059', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Madagascar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1019'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {}, 'linked_entitiy': {'pound': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q25224', 'Madagascar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1019'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'second': 'ORDINAL', 'weeks': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602', 'weeks': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q23387'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'BBC World Service - Newshour': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'BBC': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q9531', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'hospitals': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16917', 'school': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3914'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Madagascar': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Madagascar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1019', 'meteorologist': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2310145'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
10
['Myanmar , Asia Pacific : Cyclone Mocha Emergency Appeal ( No MDRMM018 ) - Bangladesh (2023-05-18)'
 'Myanmar , Asia Pacific : Cyclone Mocha Emergency Appeal ( No MDRMM018 ) - Myanmar (2023-05-18)'
 'UNICEF Myanmar Humanitarian Situation Report No . 4 ( Cyclone MOCHA ): 17 May 2023 - Myanmar (2023-05-18)'
 'Cyclone Mocha inflicts heavy damage on Myanmar Rakhine state (2023-05-16)'
 'Cyclone Mocha barrels toward Myanmar and Bangladesh (2023-05-13)']
["{'entity_type': {'Myanmar': 'GPE', 'Asia Pacific': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Bangladesh': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q902', 'Myanmar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q836', 'Asia Pacific': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4806402', 'Emergency': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2726232', 'No': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1894494'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Myanmar': 'GPE', 'Asia Pacific': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Myanmar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q836', 'Asia Pacific': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4806402', 'Emergency': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2726232', 'No': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1894494'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Myanmar': 'GPE', '4': 'CARDINAL', '17': 'CARDINAL', 'May 2023 -': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'UNICEF': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q740308', 'Myanmar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q836', '.': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q172008', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'May': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q119'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Cyclone Mocha': 'PRODUCT', 'Myanmar': 'GPE', 'Rakhine': 'NORP'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'damage': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q554774', 'Rakhine State': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q233838'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Cyclone Mocha': 'PRODUCT', 'Myanmar': 'GPE', 'Bangladesh': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'barrel': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q178506', 'Myanmar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q836', 'Bangladesh': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q902'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
11
['Khanun blows into South Korea with strong winds (2023-08-09)'
 'Typhoon Khanun lashes southern Japan , South Korea (2023-08-09)'
 'Flights cancelled as Storm Khanun hits S Korea (2023-08-11)'
 'Typhoon Khanun to hit S . Korea ; flights canceled , evacuations ordered (2023-08-09)'
 'Korea comes under influence of powerful typhoon (2023-08-09)']
["{'entity_type': {'Khanun': 'PERSON', 'South Korea': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'South Korea': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q884', 'Strong Winds': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q60738700'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Typhoon Khanun': 'PERSON', 'Japan': 'GPE', 'South Korea': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384', 'Japan': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q17', 'South Korea': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q884'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Storm Khanun': 'ORG', 'S Korea': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Flight': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q564298', 'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'S': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q682'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Typhoon Khanun': 'PERSON', 'S': 'GPE', 'Korea': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384', 'S': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q682', 'Korea': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q18097', 'flight': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q13583449', 'evacuation': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q606332'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Korea': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Korea': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q18097', 'Influence': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7741996', 'typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q140588'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
12
['Tropical cyclone Freddy causes floods , destruction , and death in Mozambique and Malawi (2023-03-22)'
 'More than 100 killed as Storm Freddy returns to Mozambique and Malawi (2023-03-13)'
 'Cyclone Freddy bears down on Mozambique (2023-03-10)'
 'Storm Freddy : Malawi services  trying their best   (2023-03-15)'
 'BBC World Service - Newsday , Nearly 200 people killed in Malawi after Storm Freddy caused devastation (2023-03-15)']
["{'entity_type': {'Freddy': 'PERSON', 'Mozambique': 'GPE', 'Malawi': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654', 'destruction': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q28754054', 'death': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029', 'Malawi': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1020'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'More than 100': 'CARDINAL', 'Storm Freddy': 'PRODUCT', 'Mozambique': 'ORG', 'Malawi': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029', 'Malawi': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1020'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Mozambique': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Malawi': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'service': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q44127'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'BBC World Service - Newsday': 'ORG', 'Nearly 200': 'CARDINAL', 'Malawi': 'GPE', 'Storm Freddy': 'PRODUCT'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'BBC': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q9531', 'people': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5', 'Malawi': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1020', 'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Devastation': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1206651'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
13
['Sub : Cyclonic Storm „ Yaas ‟ ( pronounced as „ Yass ‟) over Eastcentral Bay of Bengal ( Cyclone Alert for Odisha – West Bengal coasts - Yellow Message ) TIME OF ISSUE : 1750 HOURS IST DATED : 24 . 05 . 2021 - India (2021-05-24)'
 'Cyclone Yaas – India , Bangladesh and Sri Lanka ( IMD , SLMD , BMD , Media ) ( ECHO Daily Flash of 19 May 2021 ) - India (2021-05-24)'
 'Tropical Cyclone Yaas - May 2021 (2021-05-24)'
 'Sub : The Very Severe Cyclonic Storm  Yaas  ( pronounced as  Yass ) over northwest Bay of Bengal – ( Cyclone Warning for Odisha – West Bengal coasts - Red Message ) Time of issue : 0730 Hours IST Dated : 26 . 05 . 2021 - India (2021-05-26)'
 'India , Bangladesh - Tropical Cyclone YAAS update ( GDACS , JTWC , IMD , BMD , media ) ( ECHO Daily Flash of 26 May 2021 ) - India (2021-05-26)']
["{'entity_type': {'Yaas': 'LANGUAGE', 'Yass': 'PERSON', 'Eastcentral Bay': 'ORG', 'Odisha': 'GPE', 'West Bengal': 'GPE', '1750': 'CARDINAL', 'HOURS IST': 'TIME', '24': 'CARDINAL', '2021': 'DATE', 'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Sub': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1770447', 'Alert': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q501744', 'Yass': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1380121', 'Bay of Bengal': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q38684', 'Bengal': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q42583', 'Odisha': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q22048', 'Yellow': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q463389', 'coast': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q93352', 'TIME': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7670399', 'Issue': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q6088376', 'Hours': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q157044', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'India': 'GPE', 'Bangladesh': 'GPE', 'Sri Lanka': 'GPE', 'BMD': 'ORG', 'Media': 'ORG', '19 May 2021': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668', 'Bangladesh': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q902', 'Sri Lanka': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q854', 'IMD': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q328692', 'BMD': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2498553', 'Media': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1187804', 'Flash': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15711398', 'May': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q119'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'May 2021': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'May': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q119'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Yaas': 'PRODUCT', 'Yass': 'PERSON', 'Bay of Bengal': 'LOC', 'Odisha': 'GPE', 'West Bengal': 'GPE', '0730 Hours IST': 'TIME', '26': 'CARDINAL', '2021': 'DATE', 'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Sub': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1770447', 'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Yass': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1380121', 'Bay of Bengal': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q38684', 'Bengal': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q42583', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Odisha': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q22048', 'Message': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1042247', 'coast': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q93352', 'Time': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q43297', 'issue': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q86447', 'Hours': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q157044', 'IST': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q604055', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'India': 'GPE', 'GDACS': 'ORG', 'JTWC': 'ORG', 'IMD': 'ORG', 'BMD': 'ORG', 'ECHO Daily Flash': 'ORG', '26 May 2021': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Update': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30919232', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668', 'IMD': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q328692', 'BMD': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2498553', 'media': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1740954', 'Flash': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15711398', 'May': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q119'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
14
['Seven More Killed in Oman Following Tropical Storm Shaheen (2021-10-04)'
 '3 Killed as Cyclone Shaheen Batters Oman (2021-10-03)'
 'Four killed as cyclone Shaheen hits Oman (2021-10-04)'
 'At least three killed as Cyclone Shaheen hits Oman with strong winds and heavy rain (2021-10-03)'
 'Cyclone Shaheen hits Oman , three killed (2021-10-03)']
["{'entity_type': {'Seven': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Oman': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q842', 'Shaheen': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2915571'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'3': 'CARDINAL', 'Oman': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Oman': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q842'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Four': 'CARDINAL', 'Shaheen': 'PERSON', 'Oman': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602', 'Oman': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q842'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'At least three': 'CARDINAL', 'Cyclone Shaheen': 'PRODUCT', 'Oman': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Oman': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q842', 'Strong Winds': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q60738700', 'Heavy Rain': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q647855'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Cyclone Shaheen': 'PERSON', 'Oman': 'GPE', 'three': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Oman': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q842'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
15
['Volunteers evacuate people with disabilities ahead of Cyclone Mocha - Bangladesh (2023-05-13)'
 'Threat to refugees as cyclone nears Bangladesh , Myanmar (2023-05-13)'
 'Evacuations as Bangladesh , Myanmar brace for cyclone (2023-05-12)'
 'Mass evacuations as Myanmar takes brunt of cyclone (2023-05-14)'
 'Cyclone heads to Bangladesh , Myanmar coasts , threatening refugees - Nikkei Asia (2023-05-13)']
["{'entity_type': {'Cyclone Mocha - Bangladesh': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Volunteers': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1088192', 'people': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5', 'Disabilities': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5281167', 'Bangladesh': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q902'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Bangladesh': 'GPE', 'Myanmar': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Threat': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7797190', 'refugee': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q131572', 'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602', 'Bangladesh': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q902', 'Myanmar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q836'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Bangladesh': 'GPE', 'Myanmar': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Evacuation': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5415221', 'Bangladesh': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q902', 'Myanmar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q836', 'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Myanmar': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Mass': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q61071', 'Myanmar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q836', 'Brunt': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q21484506', 'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Bangladesh': 'GPE', 'Myanmar': 'GPE', 'Asia': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Bangladesh': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q902', 'Myanmar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q836', 'refugee': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q131572', 'Asia': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q48'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
16
['21 Dead , 96 Missing as Cyclone Batters Covid - Stricken India (2021-05-18)'
 '21 Dead , 96 Missing as Cyclone Batters Covid - stricken India (2021-05-18)'
 'Six dead as severe storm roars towards India (2021-05-16)'
 'Four dead as severe storm roars towards India (2021-05-16)'
 'Four dead as cyclone heads for west India (2021-05-17)']
["{'entity_type': {'21': 'CARDINAL', '96': 'CARDINAL', 'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Dead': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q504434', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'21': 'CARDINAL', '96': 'CARDINAL', 'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Dead': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q504434', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Six': 'CARDINAL', 'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Four': 'CARDINAL', 'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Four': 'CARDINAL', 'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602', 'West India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1151567'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
17
['Cyclone Tauktae : Indian Navy rescues 60 persons (2021-05-18)'
 'Monster cyclone Tauktae leaves 20 people dead in Covid - stricken India (2021-05-18)'
 '19 people killed , 96 onboard barge still missing as cyclone Tauktae batters India western coast - World News (2021-05-18)'
 'Daily Mirror - Cyclone Tauktae : Ninety missing at sea in the wake of storm (2021-05-18)'
 'Cyclone Tauktae : Five killed as dust storm , gales hit Karachi (2021-05-19)']
["{'entity_type': {'Indian Navy': 'ORG', '60': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Indian Navy': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q356359', 'person': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'20': 'CARDINAL', 'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Monster': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q488222', 'people': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'19': 'CARDINAL', '96': 'CARDINAL', 'Tauktae': 'ORG', 'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'people': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5', 'barge': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16518', 'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602', 'World News': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q19646492'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Daily Mirror - Cyclone Tauktae': 'ORG', 'Ninety': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'sea': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q165', 'wake': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1472138', 'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Five': 'CARDINAL', 'Karachi': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'dust storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q182878', 'gale': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2144546', 'Karachi': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8660'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
18
['Monster Cyclone Heads for Covid - Stricken India (2021-05-17)'
 'Monster Cyclone Heads for Covid - stricken India (2021-05-17)'
 'Monster cyclone makes landfall in Covid - stricken India (2021-05-17)'
 'India braces for powerful cyclone amid virus surge (2021-05-17)'
 'RTHK : Cyclone batters Covid - stricken India west coast (2021-05-18)']
["{'entity_type': {'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Monster': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q488222', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Monster': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q488222', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Monster': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q488222', 'landfall': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2551132', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668', 'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602', 'virus': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q808', 'surge': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q497332'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'India': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'RTHK': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1153480', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'West Coast': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q12606'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
19
['Cyclonic storm Jawad weakens into deep depression (2021-12-05)'
 'Cyclonic storm  Jawad  weakens into deep depression (2021-12-05)'
 'Cyclone Jawad : Depression to intensify into Cyclonic storm during next 12 hours , reach north AP - Odisha coast by Sat (2021-12-03)'
 'bengal : Deep depression intensifies into Cyclone  Jawad , to make landfall near Puri on Sunday (2021-12-03)'
 'Low - pressure system in Bay of Bengal intensifies into cyclonic storm  Jawad   (2021-12-03)']
["{'entity_type': {'Cyclonic': 'PRODUCT', 'Jawad': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Jawad': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q21497349', 'depression': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q42844'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Cyclonic': 'PRODUCT', 'Jawad': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054', 'depression': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q42844'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Cyclonic': 'LOC', 'next 12 hours': 'TIME', 'AP': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Depression': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q20001351', 'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054', 'hours': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q25235', 'AP': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q40469', 'Odisha': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q22048', 'Sat': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q131'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Cyclone': 'PRODUCT', 'Jawad': 'PERSON', 'Puri': 'GPE', 'Sunday': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'depression': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q42844', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'landfall': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2551132', 'Puri': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q207799', 'Sunday': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q132'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Bay of Bengal': 'LOC', 'Jawad  ': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'pressure system': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3267791', 'Bay': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3023608', 'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
20
['More than 80 Reported Dead in Philippines Typhoon (2021-12-19)'
 'Shocking photos show devastation in the Philippines as Typhoon Rai leaves more than 200 dead (2021-12-20)'
 'Shocking photos show devastation in the Philippines as typhoon leaves at least 109 dead (2021-12-20)'
 'Thousands flee from\xa0Philippines typhoon (2021-12-16)'
 'Five dead as powerful typhoon batters the Philippines (2021-12-17)']
["{'entity_type': {'More than 80': 'CARDINAL', 'Philippines': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Dead': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q504434', 'Philippines': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q928'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Philippines': 'GPE', 'Typhoon Rai': 'PERSON', 'more than 200': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'photos': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q125191', 'Devastation': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1206651', 'Philippines': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q928', 'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Philippines': 'GPE', 'at least 109': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'photos': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q125191', 'Devastation': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1206651', 'Philippines': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q928', 'typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q140588'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Thousands': 'CARDINAL', 'Philippines': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Thousand': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q50130655', 'Philippines': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q928'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Five': 'CARDINAL', 'Philippines': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q140588', 'Philippines': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q928'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
21
['Texas was  seconds and minute away from  monthslong  power outages (2021-02-19)'
 'Texas storm : Millions left without power and residents told to boil water (2021-02-18)'
 'With Power Largely Restored , Texans Now Face Lack of Safe Water (2021-02-20)'
 'Nearly 8 million Texans still facing disrupted water supplies after storm (2021-02-23)'
 'Power outages , water shortages as Texas shivers - International - World (2021-02-18)']
["{'entity_type': {'Texas': 'GPE', 'monthslong': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Texas': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1439', 'seconds': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q11574', 'power outage': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q828827'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Texas': 'GPE', 'Millions': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Texas': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1439', 'Millions': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1854561', 'power': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q25342', 'resident': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q572927', 'water': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q283'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Texans': 'NORP'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Restored': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7316242', 'Power': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15072855', 'Texans': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q223514', 'Lack': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16871736', 'Safe': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q39070847'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Nearly 8 million': 'CARDINAL', 'Texans': 'NORP'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Texans': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q223514', 'water supply': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1061108', 'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Texas': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'power outage': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q828827', 'water shortage': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5376358', 'Texas': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1439', 'World': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16502'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
22
['GENEVA / MOZAMBIQUE FREDDY STORM (2023-02-24)'
 'CYCLONE FREDDY WEAKENS newsdzeZimbabweNewsdzeZimbabwe (2023-02-25)'
 'Mauritius Lashed By Rains As Intense Cyclone Freddy Arrives (2023-02-20)'
 'Humanitarian charity helps communities prepare for the worst as storm Freddy heads for Mozambique .  (2023-02-21)'
 'Cyclone Freddy  severely  weakened - The Standard (2023-02-26)']
["{'entity_type': {'GENEVA': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Geneva': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q71', 'STORM': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1522462'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'WEAKENS': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'CYCLONE': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5014926'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Mauritius': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Mauritius': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1027', 'Rain': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q318485', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Freddy': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q60770292'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Freddy': 'PERSON', 'Mozambique': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'charity': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q708676', 'communities': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q177634', 'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054', 'Freddy Head': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3087038', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Standard': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7598163'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
23
['WFP / MADAGASCAR CYCLONE BATSIRAI (2022-02-08)'
 'Cyclone kills at least 10 in Madagascar , destroying homes cutting power (2022-02-06)'
 'Cyclone Batsirai Kills 6 and Displaces Thousands (2022-02-07)'
 'Cyclone Batsirai weakens after hitting Madagascar , floods expected (2022-02-06)'
 'Madagascar cyclone kills 21 , leaves homes and lives in ruins (2022-02-07)']
["{'entity_type': {'WFP': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'CYCLONE': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5014926'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'at least 10': 'CARDINAL', 'Madagascar': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Madagascar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1019', 'home': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7743', 'power': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q25342'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Cyclone Batsirai Kills 6': 'PERSON', 'Thousands': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Madagascar': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Madagascar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1019', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Madagascar': 'LOC', '21': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602', 'home': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7743', 'life': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3', 'ruins': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q109607'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
24
['Thousands in Shelters as Japan Braces for Typhoon Nanmadol (2022-09-18)'
 'Typhoon Nanmadol bears down on Japan Kyushu island – The Times Of Earth (2022-09-18)'
 'Typhoon Nanmadol : Millions told to evacuate as weather system heads for Japan (2022-09-18)'
 'Super typhoon approaches Japan (2022-09-17)'
 'Millions told to seek shelter as Japan issues  unprecedented  warning on Typhoon Nanmadol (2022-09-17)']
["{'entity_type': {'Thousands': 'CARDINAL', 'Japan': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Thousand': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q50130655', 'Japan': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q17', 'Typhoon Nanmadol': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15904596'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Japan': 'GPE', 'The Times Of Earth': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Typhoon Nanmadol': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15904596', 'Japan': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q17', 'Times': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q50008', 'Earth': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Millions': 'CARDINAL', 'Japan': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Typhoon Nanmadol': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15904596', 'Millions': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1854561', 'weather': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q11663', 'Japan': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q17'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Japan': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Super Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15941028', 'Japan': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q17'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Millions': 'CARDINAL', 'Japan': 'GPE', 'Typhoon Nanmadol': 'WORK_OF_ART'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Millions': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1854561', 'shelter': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7493941', 'warning': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7969813', 'Japan': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q17', 'Typhoon Nanmadol': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15904596'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
25
['Texas Grid Operator :  Frozen Wind Turbines Caused Power Outages   (2021-02-17)'
 'Texas snow : Millions without power in Texas as snow storm slams US (2021-02-15)'
 'Why the cold weather caused huge Texas blackouts – a visual explainer (2021-02-20)'
 'Why is Texas suffering power blackouts during the winter freeze ?  (2021-02-18)'
 'Deep freeze paralyzes Texas and knocks out its power grid (2021-02-16)']
["{'entity_type': {'Texas': 'GPE', 'Frozen Wind Turbines': 'FAC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Texas': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1439', 'Frozen': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q246283', 'Power': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15072855'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Texas': 'GPE', 'Millions': 'CARDINAL', 'US': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Texas': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1439', 'Millions': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1854561', 'power': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q25342', 'snow': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7561', 'US': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Texas': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cold Weather': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5142420', 'Texas': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1439'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Texas': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Texas': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1439', 'power': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q25342', 'winter': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1311'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Texas': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Deep Freeze': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2975945', 'Texas': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1439', 'power grid': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1096907'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
26
['22 Dead , Many Missing after 17 Inches of Rain in Tennessee (2021-08-23)'
 'The Fiji Times » Authorities locate dozens of people listed as missing in deadly Tennessee flood (2021-08-25)'
 'The Daily Herald - Authorities locate dozens of people listed as missing in Tennessee flood (2021-08-25)'
 'Tennessee flash floods kill 22 with dozens missing (2021-08-25)'
 'Boy , 2 , among ten missing in Tennessee floods after he was ripped from mum arms (2021-08-24)']
["{'entity_type': {'22': 'CARDINAL', '17 Inches': 'QUANTITY', 'Tennessee': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Dead': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q504434', 'Inches': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3797622', 'Rain': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q318485', 'Tennessee': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1509'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'The Fiji Times » Authorities': 'ORG', 'dozens': 'CARDINAL', 'Tennessee': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Authorities': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4825935', 'Fiji Times': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3071731', 'dozen': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q605704', 'people': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5', 'Tennessee': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1509'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'The Daily Herald - Authorities': 'ORG', 'dozens': 'CARDINAL', 'Tennessee': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Herald': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q6740594', 'dozen': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q605704', 'people': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5', 'Tennessee': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1509'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Tennessee': 'GPE', '22': 'CARDINAL', 'dozens': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'flash flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q860333', 'dozen': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q605704'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'2': 'DATE', 'ten': 'CARDINAL', 'Tennessee': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Tennessee': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1509', 'arms': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q728'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
27
['Tropical Storm Ana wreaks havoc for children in Madagascar , Malawi , Mozambique and Zimbabwe , warns UNICEF (2022-01-27)'
 'Photos show devastation in southern , eastern Africa as Tropical Storm Ana leaves at least 86 dead (2022-01-28)'
 'At least 77 dead after southern Africa hit by Tropical Storm Ana (2022-01-28)'
 'Tropical Storm Ana wreaks havoc across southern Africa (2022-01-28)'
 'Dozens killed in Tropical Storm Ana as southern Africa braces for more wild weather (2022-01-28)']
["{'entity_type': {'Madagascar': 'GPE', 'Malawi': 'GPE', 'Mozambique': 'GPE', 'Zimbabwe': 'GPE', 'UNICEF': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Tropical Storm Ana': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3178215', 'Havoc': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q242806', 'children': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7569', 'Madagascar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1019', 'Malawi': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1020', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029', 'Zimbabwe': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q954', 'UNICEF': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q740308'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Africa': 'LOC', 'Tropical Storm Ana': 'EVENT', 'at least 86': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Photos': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q26328552', 'Devastation': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1206651', 'Eastern Africa': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q27407', 'Tropical Storm Ana': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3178215'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'At least 77': 'CARDINAL', 'Africa': 'LOC', 'Tropical Storm': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Southern Africa': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q27394', 'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232', 'Ana': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q56290618'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Africa': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Tropical Storm Ana': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3178215', 'Havoc': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q242806', 'Southern Africa': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q27394'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Dozens': 'CARDINAL', 'Tropical Storm Ana': 'FAC', 'Africa': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Dozens': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q314553', 'Tropical Storm Ana': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3178215', 'Southern Africa': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q27394', 'Wild Weather': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q20173992'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
28
['Photos : Tornadoes Devastate Western Kentucky (2021-12-17)'
 'Death toll from US tornadoes tops 80 , Biden to visit Kentucky to survey damage (2021-12-14)'
 'Kentucky Governor : Tornado Death Toll Remains at 64 But Will Likely Rise (2021-12-14)'
 'kentucky : US tornado deaths rise to 88 , Biden to survey damage in Kentucky (2021-12-14)'
 'Kentucky tornadoes : At least 70 feared dead in Kentucky alone , governor says , after tornadoes hit central and southern US (2021-12-11)']
["{'entity_type': {'Devastate': 'GPE', 'Kentucky': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Photos': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q26328552', 'Tornado': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1416779', 'Western Kentucky': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7987999'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'US': 'GPE', '80': 'CARDINAL', 'Biden': 'PERSON', 'Kentucky': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'US': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30', 'Biden': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15980607', 'Kentucky': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1603', 'damage': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q554774'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Kentucky': 'GPE', '64': 'DATE', 'Will Likely Rise': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Kentucky Governor': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4151335', 'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'kentucky': 'GPE', 'US': 'GPE', '88': 'CARDINAL', 'Biden': 'PERSON', 'Kentucky': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Kentucky': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1603', 'US': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30', 'Biden': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15980607', 'damage': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q554774'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Kentucky': 'GPE', 'At least 70': 'CARDINAL', 'US': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Kentucky': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1603', 'governor': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q48352', 'tornado': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8081', 'US': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
29
['Tropical storm Ana death toll rises to at least 12 as homes in Malawi are destroyed (2022-01-26)'
 'At least four killed after tropical Storm Ana hits Malawi and Mozambique (2022-01-25)'
 'Tropical Storm ANA to enter Malawi tomorrow (2022-01-24)'
 'Cyclone Ana claims 20 Malawian lives (2022-01-28)'
 'Tropical storm Ana kills 46 in Madagascar , Mozambique and Malawi (2022-01-27)']
["{'entity_type': {'at least 12': 'CARDINAL', 'Malawi': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232', 'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'home': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7743', 'Malawi': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1020'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'At least four': 'CARDINAL', 'Storm Ana': 'EVENT', 'Malawi': 'GPE', 'Mozambique': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Malawi': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1020', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Tropical Storm ANA': 'ORG', 'Malawi': 'GPE', 'tomorrow': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Tropical Storm Ana': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3178215', 'Malawi': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1020', 'tomorrow': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1209716'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'20': 'CARDINAL', 'Malawian': 'NORP'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'life': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'46': 'CARDINAL', 'Madagascar': 'GPE', 'Mozambique': 'ORG', 'Malawi': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232', 'Ana': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q56290618', 'Madagascar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1019', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029', 'Malawi': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1020'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
30
['Southwest Cancels Thousands More US Flights as Weather Stays Bitter (2022-12-27)'
 'Southwest Airlines cancels all flights from several US airports sparking investigation into delays (2022-12-27)'
 'Southwest cancels thousands more US flights on weather woes (2022-12-27)'
 'Southwest Airlines flight cancellations continue to snowball (2022-12-29)'
 'Southwest Cancels Thousands More U . S . Flights On Weather Woe ...  (2022-12-29)']
["{'entity_type': {'Southwest': 'LOC', 'Thousands': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Southwest': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q503308', 'US': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30', 'Thousand': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q50130655', 'Weather': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q65070101', 'Bitter': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4918977'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Southwest Airlines': 'ORG', 'US': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Southwest Airlines': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q503308', 'flight': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q13583449', 'US': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30', 'investigation': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q21004260', 'delay': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1426138'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Southwest': 'LOC', 'thousands': 'CARDINAL', 'US': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Southwest': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q503308', 'US': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30', 'thousand': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q43016', 'weather': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q11663'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Southwest Airlines': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Southwest': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q503308'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Southwest': 'LOC', 'Thousands': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Southwest': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q503308', 'Thousand': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q50130655', 'U': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1098', 'S': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q682', 'Flight': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q564298', 'Weather': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q65070101'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
31
['Typhoon Batters Japan with Record Rain , Killing One (2022-09-19)'
 'Typhoon batters Japan with record rain , killing one - NHK (2022-09-19)'
 'Powerful Typhoon makes landfall in southern Japan as thousands take shelter (2022-09-18)'
 'Govt poised to issue special typhoon warning for Kyushu region (2022-09-17)'
 'News Navigator : Why do autumn typhoons cause extensive damage in Japan ?  (2022-09-16)']
["{'entity_type': {'Typhoon Batters': 'ORG', 'One': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Japan': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q17', 'Rain': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q318485'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Japan': 'GPE', 'one': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384', 'Japan': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q17', 'rain': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7925', 'NHK': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q212128'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Typhoon': 'LOC', 'Japan': 'GPE', 'thousands': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384', 'landfall': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2551132', 'Japan': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q17', 'thousand': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q43016', 'shelter': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7493941'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Kyushu': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q140588', 'region': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q36784'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Japan': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'News': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7019297', 'typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q140588', 'damage': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q554774', 'Japan': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q17'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
32
['India Meteorological Department Bulletin No . 32 ( ARB / 01 / 2023 ) - Sub : A ) Very Severe Cyclonic Storm  Biparjoy  ( pronounced as  Biporjoy ) over eastcentral Arabian Sea B ) Well Marked Low Pressure Are ( Time of Issue : 0900 Hours IST Dated : ... (2023-06-10)'
 '  Biparjoy  cyclone 1 , 050 km away from Oman coasts (2023-06-08)'
 'Cyclone over Arabian Sea near Indian coast to intensify in next 36 hours (2023-06-09)'
 '  Biparjoy  on course to become cyclone with longest lifespan in Arabian Sea (2023-06-12)'
 'Cyclone Biparjoy May Become Cyclone With Longest Lifespan In Arabian Sea (2023-06-12)']
["{'entity_type': {'India Meteorological Department Bulletin': 'ORG', 'Biporjoy': 'PERSON', 'Arabian Sea': 'LOC', '0900 Hours IST': 'TIME'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'A': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q9887', 'Sub': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1770447', 'India': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q668', '.': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q172008', 'ARB': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1026794', 'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'B': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q618', 'Low': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q837214', 'Time': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q43297', 'Issue': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q6088376', 'Hours': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q157044', 'IST': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q604055'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'1': 'CARDINAL', '050 km': 'QUANTITY', 'Oman': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602', 'km': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q970', 'Oman': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q842'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Arabian Sea': 'LOC', 'Indian': 'NORP', 'next 36 hours': 'TIME'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Arabian Sea': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q58705', 'coast': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q93352', 'hours': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q25235'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Biparjoy': 'PERSON', 'Arabian Sea': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'course': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1962728', 'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602', 'lifespan': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q28455121', 'Arabian Sea': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q58705'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Cyclone Biparjoy': 'PERSON', 'Arabian Sea': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Lifespan': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q6545469', 'Arabian Sea': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q58705'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
33
['NSW Floods : The sunshine is back , but this harbour not for swimming after storms (2022-03-09)'
 'NSW Weather , Floods Update : Incredible footage as Sydney hit by massive storms (2022-03-08)'
 'Australia flooded (2022-03-01)'
 'Australia weather : Urgent flood warning as SEVEN rivers are set to spill over (2022-02-23)'
 'Australia live news updates : Brisbane braces for severe flooding as Queensland death toll climbs to six , NSW reports seven Covid deaths (2022-02-26)']
["{'entity_type': {'NSW Floods': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'NSW': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3224', 'Sunshine': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q478212', 'harbour': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q283202', 'swimming': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q31920', 'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'NSW Weather': 'ORG', 'Sydney': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'NSW': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3224', 'Floods': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1090641', 'footage': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1192650', 'Sydney': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3130', 'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Australia': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Australia': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q408'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Australia': 'GPE', 'SEVEN': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Australia': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q408', 'Flood warning': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5460084', 'rivers': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4022'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Australia': 'GPE', 'Brisbane': 'GPE', 'Queensland': 'GPE', 'six': 'CARDINAL', 'NSW': 'GPE', 'seven': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Australia': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q408', 'news': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q38926', 'Brisbane': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q34932', 'flooding': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1429176', 'Queensland': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q36074', 'NSW': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3224', 'deaths': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
34
['Collapsed Florida condo to be demolished before search and rescue effort resumes (2021-07-05)'
 'Remains of collapsed Florida condo demolished ahead of tropical storm (2021-07-05)'
 'Miami condo collapse : death toll reaches 27 as demolition expands search area (2021-07-05)'
 'THE MIAMI CONDO COLLAPSE VICTIMS IDENTIFIED SO FAR (2021-06-28)'
 'Death toll rises to 27 as work resumes at collapsed Florida apartment (2021-07-05)']
["{'entity_type': {'Florida': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Florida': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q812', 'effort': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q14536140', 'Search': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16320113', 'rescue': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1341429'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Florida': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Remains': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2540185', 'Florida': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q812', 'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Miami': 'GPE', '27': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Miami': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8652', 'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'demolition': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q331483', 'area': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q11500'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'MIAMI': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Miami': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8652', 'Victim': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2747218', 'FAR': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1370687'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'27': 'CARDINAL', 'Florida': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'work': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q42213', 'Florida': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q812'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
35
['Storm Eunice : how forecasters predicted super - strong winds days before it even formed (2022-02-18)'
 'Storm Eunice  highest ever  gust of wind in England is still 51mph short of united kingdom record (2022-02-18)'
 'Storm Eunice : When was the last united kingdom red weather warning ?  (2022-02-18)'
 'Storm Eunice : Yellow warning issued as NI braces for strong winds and snow (2022-02-18)'
 'Weather maps reveal exactly how Storm Eunice will hit Coventry and Warwickshire today (2022-02-18)']
["{'entity_type': {'days': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'forecaster': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7216332', 'Strong Winds': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q60738700', 'days': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q573'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'England': 'GPE', '51mph': 'QUANTITY', 'united kingdom': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Gust of Wind': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q18221454', 'wind': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8094', 'England': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q21', 'mph': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q211256', 'record': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q178588'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Eunice': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'weather': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q11663', 'United Kingdom': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q145'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'NI': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Yellow': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q463389', 'NI': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q811', 'Strong Winds': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q60738700', 'snow': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7561'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Storm Eunice': 'PERSON', 'Coventry': 'GPE', 'Warwickshire': 'GPE', 'today': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'weather map': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q865144', 'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Coventry': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q6225', 'Warwickshire': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q23140', 'Today': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q130838'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
36
['London storms : Storm Eunice batters Europe , kills at least nine (2022-02-18)'
 'Death toll rises as Storm Eunice wreaks havoc across Europe (2022-02-18)'
 'Storm Eunice : united kingdom issues threat - to - life warning (2022-02-17)'
 'Storm Eunice : Clean up begins after storm leaves a trail of damage across united kingdom  (2022-02-19)'
 'Storm Eunice leaves 16 dead in Western Europe and tens of thousands without power (2022-02-22)']
["{'entity_type': {'London': 'GPE', 'Europe': 'LOC', 'at least nine': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'London': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q84', 'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Europe': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q458'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Storm Eunice': 'PRODUCT', 'Europe': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Havoc': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q242806', 'Europe': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q458'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'United Kingdom': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q145', 'warning': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7969813', 'threat': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q707125', 'life': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054', 'trail': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q628179', 'damage': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q554774', 'United Kingdom': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q145'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'16': 'CARDINAL', 'Western Europe': 'LOC', 'tens of thousands': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Western Europe': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q27496', 'thousand': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q43016', 'ten': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q23806', 'power': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q25342'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
37
['Storm Eunice batters Britain and Ireland (2022-02-18)'
 'Storm Eunice batters England and Ireland (2022-02-18)'
 'Hilarious memes flood Twitter as Storm Eunice devastates Britain (2022-02-18)'
 'Live updates : The chaos and carnage caused by Storm Eunice (2022-02-18)'
 'What you need to know about Storm Eunice in Norfolk (2022-02-17)']
["{'entity_type': {'Eunice': 'PERSON', 'Britain': 'GPE', 'Ireland': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Britain': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3240725', 'Ireland': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q22890'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'England': 'GPE', 'Ireland': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'England': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q21', 'Ireland': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q22890'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Britain': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'meme': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q978', 'Twitter': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q918', 'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Britain': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3240725'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Eunice': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Updates': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q23020316', 'chaos': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2419662', 'Carnage': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q55607777', 'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Norfolk': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q632212', 'Norfolk': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q49231'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
38
['Typhoon Doksuri downgraded to tropical storm in China (2023-07-29)'
 'Typhoon Doksuri : At least 20 dead in Beijing as heavy rains cause floods and force thousands from their homes (2023-08-01)'
 'Update : China renews most severe alert for Typhoon Doksuri (2023-07-28)'
 'Typhoon Doksuri unlikely to affect Vietnamese mainland (2023-07-27)'
 'Typhoon Doksuri rapidly intensifies , may hit Philippines (2023-07-24)']
["{'entity_type': {'Typhoon Doksuri': 'PERSON', 'China': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384', 'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232', 'China': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q148'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'At least 20': 'CARDINAL', 'Beijing': 'GPE', 'thousands': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384', 'Beijing': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q956', 'Heavy Rain': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q647855', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654', 'thousand': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q43016', 'home': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7743'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'China': 'GPE', 'Typhoon Doksuri': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Update': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30919232', 'China': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q148', 'alert': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4716232', 'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Typhoon Doksuri': 'PERSON', 'Vietnamese': 'NORP'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Philippines': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Typhoon': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q151384', 'Philippines': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q928'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
39
['New ZealandState of emergency declared in Auckland after months rain in a night (2023-01-27)'
 'Political Roundup : How authorities failed Aucklanders in an emergency (2023-01-29)'
 'BREAKING : Auckland flooding emergency highlights\xa0Mayors incompetence\xa0and how climate change can no longer be denied (2023-01-28)'
 '3 dead , state of emergency in New Zealand largest city after record rainfall (2023-01-28)'
 'New Zealand floods : Auckland mayor admits incorrect emergency management decisions (2023-01-30)']
["{'entity_type': {'Auckland': 'GPE', 'months': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'New': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q14754876', 'emergency': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5070802', 'Auckland': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q37100', 'months': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5151', 'night': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q575'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Aucklanders': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Roundup': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q905161', 'authorities': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q36524', 'emergency': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5070802'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Auckland': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q37100', 'Mayors': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7750742', 'climate change': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7942'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'3': 'CARDINAL', 'New Zealand': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'state of emergency': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q216227', 'emergency': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5070802', 'city': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q515', 'Zealand': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q25535', 'New': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q14754876', 'rainfall': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7925'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'New Zealand': 'GPE', 'Auckland mayor': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'New': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q14754876', 'Auckland': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q37100', 'emergency': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5070802'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
40
['President Biden plans to visit Texas and declare a major disaster (2021-02-20)'
 'Joe Biden says he is considering visit to disaster - hit Texas (2021-02-19)'
 'Biden approves major disaster declaration for Texas amid deadly winter storm (2021-02-20)'
 'Texas weather crisis : Joe Biden to declare major disaster as he plans visit (2021-02-20)'
 'Biden declares major disaster in Texas as federal aid ...  (2021-02-20)']
["{'entity_type': {'Biden': 'PERSON', 'Texas': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'President': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30945670', 'Texas': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1439', 'Major Disaster': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3546910'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Joe Biden': 'PERSON', 'Texas': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Joe Biden': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q6279', 'visit': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q17126187', 'Texas': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1439'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Biden': 'ORG', 'Texas': 'GPE', 'winter': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Biden': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15980607', 'disaster': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3839081', 'Texas': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1439', 'winter storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q75079023'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Texas': 'GPE', 'Joe Biden': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Joe Biden': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q6279', 'Texas': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1439', 'Major Disaster': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3546910'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Biden': 'PERSON', 'Texas': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Biden': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15980607', 'Major Disaster': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3546910', 'Texas': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1439', 'aid': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2827815'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
41
['NOAA predicts a busy 2021 hurricane season , but not like last year (2021-05-20)'
 'NOAA predicts another above - normal hurricane season - World (2021-05-24)'
 'Hurricane Season Is About to Start Early -- Again (2021-05-21)'
 '2021 will have an  above average  number of hurricanes , experts warn (2021-05-21)'
 'Hurricane Season - What it Is (2021-06-03)']
["{'entity_type': {'NOAA': 'ORG', '2021': 'DATE', 'last year': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'NOAA': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q214700', 'Hurricane Season': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2031385', 'Last Year': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5274490'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'NOAA': 'ORG', 'hurricane season - World': 'EVENT'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'NOAA': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q214700', 'Hurricane Season': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2031385', 'World': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16502'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Hurricane Season': 'EVENT'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Hurricane Season': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2031385'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'2021': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'number': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q11563', 'hurricane': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q13516761', 'experts': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q381160'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Hurricane Season': 'EVENT'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Hurricane Season': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2031385'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
42
['After the tornado , half of a Kentucky town  is just gone   (2021-12-12)'
 'Biden Declares Major Disaster In Kentucky After Tornadoes Kill Dozens (2021-12-13)'
 'Kentucky tornado survivors recall frightening moments ,  It was awful   (2021-12-13)'
 'Biden heads to Kentucky as residents cope with death , destruction left by deadly tornados (2021-12-15)'
 'Biden heads to Kentucky as residents cope with death , destruction left by deadly tornadoes (2021-12-15)']
["{'entity_type': {'half': 'CARDINAL', 'Kentucky': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'tornado': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8081', 'half': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2114394', 'Kentucky': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1603'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Biden': 'ORG', 'Kentucky': 'GPE', 'Dozens': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Biden': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15980607', 'Major Disaster': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3546910', 'Kentucky': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1603', 'Dozens': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q314553'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Kentucky': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Kentucky': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1603', 'moment': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q48103'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Biden': 'PERSON', 'Kentucky': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Biden': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15980607', 'Kentucky': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1603', 'resident': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q572927', 'death': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4', 'destruction': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q28754054', 'tornado': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8081'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Biden': 'PERSON', 'Kentucky': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Biden': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15980607', 'Kentucky': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1603', 'resident': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q572927', 'death': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q4', 'destruction': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q28754054', 'tornado': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8081'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
43
['Surfside condo demolition : Explosives bring down rest of collapsed Miami building (2021-07-05)'
 'Entire Miami building to be demolished amid fears of approaching storm (2021-07-03)'
 'Officials will demolish remainder of collapsed Florida condo before tropical storm hits (2021-07-03)'
 'Demolition crews move in at collapsed Florida condo tower amid storm fears (2021-07-04)'
 'Watch : Remains of collapsed Florida apartment block demolished ahead of storm (2021-07-05)']
["{'entity_type': {'Miami': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'condo': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q161851', 'explosives': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q12870', 'rest': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q879844', 'Miami': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8652'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Miami': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Miami': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8652', 'fear': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q44619', 'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Florida': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'official': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q716711', 'remainder': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q846677', 'Florida': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q812', 'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Florida': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'crew': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q159354', 'Florida': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q812', 'Storm Fear': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q17125471'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Florida': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Remains': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2540185', 'apartment block': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q13402009', 'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
44
['20 dead as storms hit Mozambique and Uganda (2022-01-26)'
 'Tropical storm Ana kills 34 in Madagascar , two in Mozambique (2022-01-25)'
 'Tropical Storm Ana Kills 86 In Southern Africa (2022-01-28)'
 'Tropical Storm Ana kills two in central Mozambique - Xinhua (2022-01-25)'
 'Tropical storm Ana kills 18 in Mozambique - Xinhua (2022-01-27)']
["{'entity_type': {'20': 'CARDINAL', 'Mozambique': 'GPE', 'Uganda': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029', 'Uganda': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1036'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'34': 'CARDINAL', 'Madagascar': 'GPE', 'two': 'CARDINAL', 'Mozambique': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232', 'Ana': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q56290618', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029', 'Madagascar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1019'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'86': 'CARDINAL', 'Southern Africa': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232', 'Ana': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q56290618', 'Southern Africa': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q27394'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'two': 'CARDINAL', 'Mozambique': 'NORP'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Tropical Storm Ana': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3178215', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'18': 'CARDINAL', 'Mozambique': 'NORP'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232', 'Ana': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q56290618', 'Mozambique': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1029'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
45
['  Bomb  cyclone wreaks havoc on US holiday travel (2022-12-24)'
 '  Bomb cyclone  in North America wreaks havoc causing power outages and travel chaos (2022-12-24)'
 'How Could The US Bomb Cyclone Affect united kingdom Weather ?  (2022-12-29)'
 'Deadly US bomb cyclone will spark flooding , downpours and gale force winds in the united kingdom  (2022-12-29)'
 'Met Office explains how America winter  bomb cyclone  will hit united kingdom  (2022-12-30)']
["{'entity_type': {'US': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q79602', 'Havoc': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q242806', 'US': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'North America': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'bomb cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2909653', 'North America': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q49', 'Havoc': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q242806', 'power outage': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q828827', 'travel': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q61509'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {}, 'linked_entitiy': {'kingdom': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q36732'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'US': 'GPE', 'the united kingdom': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'bomb cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2909653', 'flooding': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1429176', 'Downpour': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5945989', 'wind': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8094', 'United Kingdom': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q145'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Met Office': 'ORG', 'America': 'GPE', 'winter': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Met Office': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1851405', 'bomb cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2909653', 'United Kingdom': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q145'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
46
['At least 76 people killed in floods and landslides as tropical cyclone hits Indonesia and East Timor (2021-04-05)'
 'Dozens of people dead in Indonesia and East Timor following floods and landslides (2021-04-04)'
 'Dozens dead as torrential rain leads to floods and landslides in Indonesia and Timor - Leste (2021-04-04)'
 'More than 90 dead after floods and landslides destroy communities in Indonesia and Timor - Leste (2021-04-05)'
 'More than 100 dead after floods and landslides destroy communities in Indonesia and Timor - Leste (2021-04-05)']
["{'entity_type': {'At least 76': 'CARDINAL', 'Indonesia': 'GPE', 'East Timor': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'people': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654', 'landslide': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q167903', 'tropical cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8092', 'Indonesia': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q252', 'East Timor': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q574'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Dozens': 'CARDINAL', 'Indonesia': 'GPE', 'East Timor': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Dozens': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q314553', 'people': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654', 'landslide': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q167903'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Dozens': 'CARDINAL', 'Indonesia': 'GPE', 'Timor': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Dozens': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q314553', 'torrential rain': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2238184', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654', 'landslide': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q167903', 'Indonesia': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q252', 'Timor': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q83067'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'More than 90': 'CARDINAL', 'Indonesia': 'GPE', 'Timor': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654', 'landslide': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q167903', 'communities': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q177634', 'Indonesia': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q252', 'Timor': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q83067'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'More than 100': 'CARDINAL', 'Indonesia': 'GPE', 'Timor': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654', 'landslide': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q167903', 'communities': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q177634', 'Indonesia': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q252', 'Timor': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q83067'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
47
['Italy flooded , at least eight victims PHOTO / VIDEO (2023-05-18)'
 'Flood nightmare hits Italian towns with four dead (2023-05-17)'
 'Italian Red Cross helps hundreds affected by deadly floods in Emilia - Romagna region (2023-05-20)'
 'Italy extends red weather alert due to rainfall and deadly floods (2023-05-21)'
 'Italy floods show cost of ignoring climate change (2023-05-24)']
["{'entity_type': {'Italy': 'GPE', 'at least eight': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Italy': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q38', 'victims': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1851760', 'PHOTO': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7187664'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Italian': 'NORP', 'four': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'nightmare': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q192692', 'town': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3957'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Italian Red Cross': 'ORG', 'hundreds': 'CARDINAL', 'Emilia - Romagna': 'PERSON'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Italian Red Cross': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q913903', 'hundred': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q313354', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654', 'region': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q36784'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Italy': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Italy': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q38', 'weather': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q11663', 'rainfall': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7925', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Italy': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Italy': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q38', 'cost': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q240673', 'climate change': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7942'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
48
['Feds promise massive aid for Hurricane Ian victims , as rescues continue in Florida (2022-10-03)'
 'Labour Ministry leads relief efforts for communities affected by Tropical Storm Ian (2022-09-30)'
 'US government vows major aid for Hurricane Ian victims as rescues continue (2022-10-02)'
 'Hurricane Ian : How can you apply for FEMA assistance if you were affected ?  (2022-10-02)'
 'Help for Hurricane Ian Survivors Comes From Israel (2022-10-03)']
["{'entity_type': {'Hurricane Ian': 'EVENT', 'Florida': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Fed': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q53536', 'aid': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2827815', 'Hurricane': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q194251', 'rescue': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1341429', 'Florida': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q812'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Labour Ministry': 'ORG', 'Tropical Storm': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'labour ministry': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q12813215', 'relief': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q245117', 'communities': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q177634', 'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232', 'Ian': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q18336315'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'US': 'GPE', 'Hurricane Ian': 'EVENT'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'US government': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q48525', 'aid': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2827815', 'Hurricane': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q194251', 'rescue': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1341429'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Hurricane Ian': 'EVENT', 'FEMA': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Hurricane': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q194251', 'FEMA': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q503010'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Israel': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Survivor': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q28856068', 'Israel': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q801'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
49
['Hurricane Ida makes landfall in Louisiana with winds stronger than Katrina (2021-08-29)'
 'Hurricane Ida  will be one of worst storms to hit Louisiana in 170 year and is set to arrive within hours (2021-08-29)'
 'Ida downgraded to a tropical storm , 16 hours after striking in Louisiana as a Category 4 hurricane , forecasters say (2021-08-30)'
 'US : Hurricane Ida death toll rises as recovery efforts continue (2021-09-05)'
 'Outside of New Orleans , an Even Longer Road to Hurricane Ida Recovery (2021-09-05)']
["{'entity_type': {'Hurricane Ida': 'EVENT', 'Louisiana': 'GPE', 'Katrina': 'EVENT'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Hurricane Ida': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2586158', 'landfall': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2551132', 'Louisiana': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1588', 'wind': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q8094'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Hurricane Ida': 'EVENT', 'one': 'CARDINAL', 'Louisiana': 'GPE', '170 year': 'DATE', 'hours': 'TIME'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Hurricane Ida': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2586158', 'storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q81054', 'Louisiana': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1588', 'year': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q577', 'hours': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q25235'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'16 hours': 'TIME', 'Louisiana': 'GPE', '4': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Ida': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q15087230', 'Tropical Storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16958232', 'hours': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q25235', 'Louisiana': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1588', 'hurricane': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q13516761', 'category': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q719395', 'forecaster': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7216332'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'US': 'GPE', 'Hurricane Ida': 'EVENT'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'US': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30', 'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'recovery': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q2135807'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'New Orleans': 'GPE', 'Hurricane Ida Recovery': 'EVENT'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Road': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q738052', 'New Orleans': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q34404', 'Hurricane': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q194251'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
50
['  Perfect storm : Floods spark deadly spider warning (2021-03-24)'
 'Australians Warned Of Deadly Spider  Plague  After Floods (2021-03-24)'
 'After days of floods , Australians warned of deadly spider  plague   (2021-03-24)'
 'SAMAA - Australians warned of deadly spider  plague  after floods (2021-03-24)'
 'Australians Warned Of Deadly Spider Boom After Floods (2021-03-24)']
["{'entity_type': {}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Perfect storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3983144', 'Flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3363652', 'spider': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1357'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Australians Warned Of': 'ORG', 'Floods': 'EVENT'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Australians': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1318423', 'Spider': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q982558', 'Flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3363652'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'days': 'DATE', 'Australians': 'NORP'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'days': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q573', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654', 'Australians': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1318423', 'plague': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q42005'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'SAMAA - Australians': 'NORP'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Australians': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1318423', 'plague': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q42005', 'flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1564654'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Australians Warned Of Deadly Spider Boom After Floods': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Australians': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1318423', 'Spider Boom': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q7577014', 'Flood': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q3363652'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
51
['Madagascar death toll from Cyclone Batsirai rises sharply (2022-02-09)'
 'Death toll from Cyclone Batsirai in Madagascar rises to 120 - state agency (2022-02-11)'
 'Madagascar Cyclone Toll Rises To 30 (2022-02-09)'
 'Death Toll From Cyclone Batsirai Rises To 21 In Madagascar – UN (2022-02-09)'
 'Cyclone death toll jumps to 111 in Madagascar (2022-02-11)']
["{'entity_type': {'Madagascar': 'LOC', 'Cyclone Batsirai': 'LOC'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Cyclone Batsirai': 'PRODUCT', 'Madagascar': 'LOC', '120': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Madagascar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1019', 'state agency': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q327333'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Madagascar Cyclone': 'LOC', '30': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Madagascar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1019'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'21': 'CARDINAL', 'Madagascar': 'GPE', 'UN': 'ORG'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'Cyclone': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q362264', 'Madagascar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1019', 'UN': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1065'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'111': 'CARDINAL', 'Madagascar': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'Death Toll': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q5247224', 'Madagascar': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1019'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
52
['Illinois dust storm : At least six dead , 30 in hospital after US highway crash (2023-05-02)'
 'Six die in highway pile - up as dust storm blinds drivers (2023-05-02)'
 'At least six dead after dust storm causes crashes in Illinois (2023-05-02)'
 'Dust storm in Illinois leaves at least 6 dead (2023-05-02)'
 'US : Multiple dead after dust storm causes highway pileup – DW – 05 / 01 / 2023 (2023-05-01)']
["{'entity_type': {'Illinois': 'GPE', 'At least six': 'CARDINAL', '30': 'CARDINAL', 'US': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'dust storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q182878', 'hospital': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q16917', 'US': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Six': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'highway': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q269949', 'dust storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q182878', 'driver': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1033951'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'At least six': 'CARDINAL', 'Illinois': 'GPE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'dust storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q182878', 'crash': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q238053', 'Illinois': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1204'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'Illinois': 'GPE', 'at least 6': 'CARDINAL'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'dust storm': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q182878', 'Illinois': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q1204'}}"
 "{'entity_type': {'US': 'GPE', 'DW': 'ORG', '05 / 01 / 2023': 'DATE'}, 'linked_entitiy': {'US': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q30', 'DW': 'https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q153770'}}"]
-----------------------------------------------
53
['Australia Floods Worsen , Thousands Flee Sydney Homes (2022-07-05)'
 'Sydney Floods Burden 50 , 000 around Australia Largest City (2022-07-05)'
 'Thousands Told to Evacuate Before  Life - threatening  Sydney Flood (2022-07-03)'
 'NSW flood update , conserve water alert : Full list of Sydney suburbs that need to conserve water after freak weather event including Claremont Meadows , Penrith and Jordan Springs (2022-07-06)'
 'Residents call for better dam management in Sydney flood disaster (2022-07-05)']
